<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Steven Korvin&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Steven Korvin&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 20:22:57 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stevenkorvin.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>There&#39;s Nothing to Buy</title>
      <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/theres-nothing-to-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 20:22:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/theres-nothing-to-buy/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;All my life, I&amp;rsquo;ve never understood what, to me, is commercialist nonsense. It&amp;rsquo;s not my ethics or my values. I just don&amp;rsquo;t understand it all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Life has been tough for me, though, so I&amp;rsquo;ve bought a lot of things with my limited income. Buying all those things had satiated personal stress, but it gave me additional stress. I don&amp;rsquo;t care about the things that I&amp;rsquo;ve bought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After two years struggling in Computer Science doing school online at Oregon State University, I&amp;rsquo;m now doing well in my Cybersecurity Technology program at University of Maryland Global Campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten rid of all those nonsensical hobbies in my life. Those hobbies helped pass the time and they stimulated my mind. They were overstimulation, though. I can&amp;rsquo;t watch a movie or a TV show. I have difficulties with music. Now, I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten video games out of my life, too. So, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on information security-related things in the ways that I&amp;rsquo;m able to. I&amp;rsquo;ll be attending BSides Connecticut on September 21st!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Move to Anatole Theme</title>
      <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/move-to-anatole-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 06:04:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/move-to-anatole-theme/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With the uBlogger theme no longer maintained, I have moved this site to the Anatole Hugo theme, which can be found here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/lxndrblz/anatole&#34;&gt;https://github.com/lxndrblz/anatole&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Credit for this theme goes to all contributors behind its development.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EVC Project Photographs</title>
      <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/evc-project-photographs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 03:13:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/evc-project-photographs/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I tried to make photographs of the Electric Vehicle Conversion project look snazzy in the uBlogger Hugo theme. I&amp;rsquo;m just going to direct you to an album in my PixelFed account instead: &lt;a href=&#34;http://link.stevenkorvin.com/PG8kwp&#34;&gt;http://link.stevenkorvin.com/PG8kwp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>