<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Steven Korvin&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Steven Korvin&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 20:48:58 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stevenkorvin.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One Day at a Time</title>
      <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/one-day-at-a-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 20:48:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/one-day-at-a-time/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;School had been very rough for me the past few years. From 2021 to 2022, I was trying to figure out what to do next after Bergen Community College. From fall 2022 to fall 2024, Computer Science at Oregon State University wasn&amp;rsquo;t working out for me. I started my first term at University of Maryland Global Campus in August, and I tried extra hard because I wanted to succeed. I threw away all my hobbies, I deleted some social media accounts, and I deleted my personal data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, the need for proper mental stimulation soon arose. After two weeks of trying to focus solely on a trade and a professional life, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t handle that anymore. There&amp;rsquo;s something to be said about &amp;ldquo;the definition of insanity,&amp;rdquo; though. I&amp;rsquo;m not going back to Twitter/X, Mastodon, or Bluesky. It&amp;rsquo;s the free for all nature of those platforms where anyone can talk about whatever when I need things to be focused on my hobbies and interests. Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve never understood the act of &amp;ldquo;retweeting.&amp;rdquo;  While I require Discord for school purposes, I&amp;rsquo;m not going to chase down all the Discord servers that I was a part of. I just don&amp;rsquo;t understand Discord.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One could talk about the uselessness of social media, but I&amp;rsquo;ve found what works best for me when I&amp;rsquo;ve tried so many things.  Yes, I had two posts on this site this past week that I&amp;rsquo;ve since deleted. Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;m now picking up the pieces of what I did about two weeks ago. I have three hard drives. All of my data alphabetically after the Myrient directory in the root of the third hard drive is lost. That includes my &amp;ldquo;Retro Computing and Windows 9x&amp;rdquo; directory. I know that I could run a scan on the drive using data recovery tools, but there would be a million files that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t recognize if I did that. The best that I can do there is use one of those data recovery tools for inspiration on what to look for online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of my files related to the Yuzu emulator might be tough for find, and I know that my Gravis Ultrasound preconfigured directory for emulators that I found on VOGONS is offline. Thankfully, someone else on VOGONS created a new directory that is mirrored on the Internet Archive. People tell me this all the time, but it&amp;rsquo;s true that I have to take things one day at a time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Move to Anatole Theme</title>
      <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/move-to-anatole-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 06:04:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/move-to-anatole-theme/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With the uBlogger theme no longer maintained, I have moved this site to the Anatole Hugo theme, which can be found here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/lxndrblz/anatole&#34;&gt;https://github.com/lxndrblz/anatole&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Credit for this theme goes to all contributors behind its development.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EVC Project Photographs</title>
      <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/evc-project-photographs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 03:13:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/post/evc-project-photographs/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I tried to make photographs of the Electric Vehicle Conversion project look snazzy in the uBlogger Hugo theme. I&amp;rsquo;m just going to direct you to an album in my PixelFed account instead: &lt;a href=&#34;http://link.stevenkorvin.com/PG8kwp&#34;&gt;http://link.stevenkorvin.com/PG8kwp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>